みんな 必死で捜している
距離のいらない もう１人を
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
おかげで小さく怖がりの人間は
困っている
こんなに星が大きくては
人との距離の測り方が分からない
60億もの人間がいるのに
みんなそれぞれ とても１人で
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかし VIP なエア・フォース
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの どうして？
知らない間に
創造主という者がいたとして
きっと彼は この星を大きく創りすぎたのだ
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
If there was a creator,
I’m convinced he made the world too big.
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
Because of that, small, timid people are troubled.
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
On such a big planet,
one cannot gauge the distance between people.
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
Even though there are six billion people,
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
each individual is extremely alone.
Everyone searches desperately…
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
…for the other person who doesn’t want to be distanced.
Chapter 18: "Sister's Confessional"
I know I’ve begun living under the bridge,
橋の下で暮らし始めて分かったことだが
but my lover Nino-san
俺の恋人ニノさんは寝ている時
wanders aimlessly and indifferently in search of comfortable places to sleep.
快適に眠れる場所を探して
うろつく習性があり
ん？ またここか
I’m here again.
Nino-san, that’s my line.
ニノさん それ俺のセリフ
寒い夜には よく俺の部屋に避難してくる
On cold nights, she often seeks refuge in my room.
朝食 食べていきますか？
Would you like to have breakfast?
Nah. I’m going home to sleep again.
いい 帰って二度寝だ…
Well then, good night.
じゃあ おやすみなさい
Nino…
ニノ…
The
same
week
follo
wing
Sun
day
Ma
ss
The same
week
following
Sunday Mass
For confession?
懺悔室に？
Sorry, but it’s important.
すまんな 大事な話なんだ
Yeah, that’s fine.
ええ いいですけど…
Confessional
Even though I’ve been told to go in there and wait…
先に行って待ってろって言われたけど…
懺悔室に入るのって初めてだなあ
This is the first time I’ve gone into a confessional.
失礼しまーす
Excuse me.
Confessional
よう
Hey.
Been waitin’ for you
待ってたぜ このクソネクタイ
and yer crappy necktie.
うわっ！ ほほほ 星？
なんでお前がここにいるんだ！
H-Hoshi!
Why are you over there?
ふん 俺がシスターに
呼んでもらったんだよ
I got Sister to call you here.
Never thought you’d dare show yer face
あんなことをしたそばから
俺に呼ばれたら
since you did something so bold right in front’a me!
顔出せねえだろうと思ってなあ
はあ？ 俺が何したって言うんだよ？
What are you implying I did?
Quit playin’ dumb.
しらばっくれんじゃねえ…
俺はなあ 見てたんだよ
You know… I saw it.
Nino was leavin’ your house early in the morning the day before yesterday!
一昨日の朝早く！
ニノがお前の家から出てくるのをなあ！
So what?
それが何？ よくあることじゃん
Happens a lot.
Hey.
おい
ニノみたいに最高にキュートな子と
一晩…
You spend a night with someone as amazingly cute as Nino,
and in a situation like this, you say “so what?”
そんな状況を“それが何？”で
終わらせられる男がいるわけねえだろー！
I’m not the kind of man who’ll yet you get away with that!
はあ？ お前 何変な勘違い
What strange things are you–
はあ！ 言っとくけどなあ！
そうやって白ぁ切れるのも今のうちだけだぜ
I’ll tell you this!
This is yer last chance to come clean.
Now, please allow me to introduce…
さあ ご登場下さい！
Come forth!
出でよ 恐怖の人間嘘発見器！
The dreaded human lie detector,
Sister!
シスタアーーー！
Could you stop introducing me that way?
その紹介の仕方はやめんか
Sister.
シスター！ どういうことなんですか？
What is this about?
Well, it’s my duty to judge if your explanations are true or not.
まあ 要は嘘の証言かどうかを
判断する役だな
Besides, I can’t refuse someone who’s crying.
それに泣かれると断れんのだ
えっ え？ なっ 泣いてねーよ！
I-I didn’t cry!
Anyway, now the preparations are all set.
とにかく これで準備オッケーだ
Now then, Recruit-kun,
さあて リクルート君…
how far have you gone with Nino?
ニノにどこまで手を出しやがったか
洗いざらい吐いてもらおうか！
We’ll make you spit it all out!
Hold on.
おっと 言っとくが
もう嘘は通用しないぜー？
I’ll tell ya that lying won’t work.
Because of his profession, Sister can see through every lie with 100% accuracy in the confessional!
シスターは職業柄か 懺悔室の中でなら
100％嘘を見破れるんだからなあ！
いや それすごくないっ？
Wait, that’s really amazing!
へえ… へえ… へえ… ふん！
Give it up, Rec!
観念しろリク！ さあ行くぜ！
Now, let’s begin!
Have you been on a date with Nino?
お前はニノと
デートしたことはありますか？
Why are you starting that far back?
なぜ そんな遠くからなんだ？
My heart is
made of glass!
Just like when you get into a pool,
My heart is
made of glass!
プールに入る時だって 心臓のために
足から水をかけていくだろうが！
My heart is
made of glass!
for your heart’s sake, test the water with your foot first, right?
Chapter 19: "Bromance"
Don’t you need to verify that lies don’t work on me?
私に嘘が通用しないことの
証明はせんでいいのか？
It’s fine.
いいですよ そんなの 嘘つく気ないですし
I’m not going to lie anyway.
Moreover, if Sister decided something was black,
それに シスターが本気で黒と言えば
白も黒になると思いますし
I think it’d turn black even if it had been white.
ふ… そう言ってくれるか
Is that how you see me?
You’re even being a Sister when you’re obviously a Brother.
ブラザーをシスターにしてる時点で
Anyway, that’s the first question.
とにかく第１問だよ！ 答えろ リク！
Answer it, Rec!
I know, quit fussing.
分かってるよ うるさいなあ
えーと… デートね
Well, a date, huh?
Had a date…
デートをしたことは… あー…
あれ そういえばないですね
Oh?
Now that I think about it, we haven’t.
You haven’t?
ない？
It’s true.
本当だぞ
デートをしたことがない？
お泊りがあるのに？
You haven’t gone on a date?
Even though she stays the night?
Speaking of which, you said she often spends the night, didn’t you?
ていうか お前さっきお泊りが
よくあるっつったよなあ？
How many times has she stayed over so far?
今まで何回あるんだ？
I’ve never counted.
そんなの数えてないよ
N-No way…
そ… そんな…
It’s true.
本当だぞ
If it was me, each and every time,
俺だったら… 毎回 毎回　カレンダーと
手帳の両方にハートマークつけて
I’d etch it on my calender, notebook, and even in my heart,
and make them all my mementos.
全部 記念日にして 毎年…
And every year…
Are you getting back to it, Hoshi?
戻ってこんか 星
Well, but you know,
いや でもよ
そのお泊りって 要はデートだろ？
spending the night is a date too, right?
No, it’s not.
違いますよ 寝てるだけです
She was just sleeping, that’s all.
She goes home as soon as she wakes up.
起きたらすぐ帰って頂いてますけど？
It’s true.
本当だ
はは… ははっ デートもまだだというのに？
ははっ 家に連れ込んで？
Even though you said you’ve not had a date,
you brought her to your house.
は！ ふざけるな ニノは
てめえのオモチャじゃねんだぞ！
Quit screwing around.
Nino’s not your toy!
I’m more worried about the depth of your delusions.
お前の妄想力のほうが 俺は心配だ…
Even so, I never thought he’d really cry.
にしても まさか本当に泣くとは
It’s irritating that his misunderstandings are way off base,
むかつくから どこまでも
勘違いさせとこうと思ったけど…
but he’s frantic in his own way.
星も星なりに必死なんだな
Enough of this already.
もういいよ
What did you say, you bastard?!
何だとこの野郎！ 全然よくねえよ！
This isn’t nearly enough!
Die, you bast–
I haven’t done anything with Nino-san!
ほんとに なにもしてないよ
ニノさんには！
How the hell can I believe that?!
信じられるわけ…！
Sister!
シスター 俺 嘘ついてますか？
Was I lying?
Rec hasn’t done anything, Hoshi.
リクは なにもしてないぞ 星よ
なあっ！ あ…
How about taking that with joy?
喜んだらどうだ？
Seriously?
マジで…？ じゃ リクルート お前…
So, Recruit, you…
I what?
何だよ
This is rare. Has he reflected on his errors?
珍しい 反省したのか？
It’s not likely that I’ll get along with this guy, but…
こいつと仲良くやろうなんて気は
さらさらないけど…
Well, in this case, I guess we could make up.
まあ 今回の分の仲直りくらいなら
Y-You’re… Well, are you actually…
お お前ってよ… あ その… 実は…
…a homo?
ホモ？
Even though I hate you quite a bit,
you hate me just as much, right?
俺も相当お前のこと嫌いだけど
お前も相当俺のこと嫌いだよな？
Yeah.
ああ いつだって殴りたいね
I’ll always want to beat you up.
Chapter 20: "Rec's Determination"
ふへえ へへへへ はははは…！
Seriously?
マジでえ？ うっそー！
はっはっはっはっ…！
No way!
うふ あっ もうメンゴメンゴ！
Ah! Sorry, sowwy!
That means I don’t have to take it back… That Rec’s a chicken.
俺 リクがチキンの甲斐性なしだってことぉ
んんんー 知らなくってさ
You’re a joke, Rec!
ああ そう…
I see.
Endure it.
こらえろ… これ以上の面倒はごめんだ
I don’t need any more trouble than this.
ここは何とか耐えて…
I’ll endure it somehow.
Well, ya know,
まあ あれだよなあ
お前見るからにモテなさそうだもんな！
looking at you, you don’t look like the popular sort.
Even your Valentine’s chocolates are all from relatives or friends, right?
バレンタインのチョコも
身内からもらってた口だろ？
Aw gee, you still have a long way to go.
何だあ やっぱりまだまだ
I still stand a chance then, right?
俺にもぜーんぜん
チャンスがあるじゃねえかあ！
おい どこ行くんだよ星！
Hey, where are you going, Hoshi?!
To ask Nino for a date.
ニノをデートに誘いにだよ
In place of the useless guy who never takes her out,
彼女をどこにも連れてってあげられない
ダメ男の代わりに
I have to give her happiness instead.
俺が幸せにしてあげないとねえー！
Probably three thousand.
３桁だ
The number of chocolates I get on Valentine’s every year.
毎年頂くチョコレートの数ですよ
It’s true.
本当だぞ
はっ？ そんなマンガみたいな数？
Such an unrealistic number?
It’s only natural.
当然でしょう
I’m gifted with intelligence, good looks, and a promising future.
才色兼備！ 眉目秀麗！ 将来有望！
If I’m not popular, who would be?
この俺がモテなくて誰がモテるんです？
Hoshi-kun, thanks for your advice.
星君 アドバイスありがとう
ああん？
As her boyfriend, it’s my job to be the one to ask Nino out on a date!
ニノさんをデートに誘うのは
恋人である この俺の仕事です！
Damn you, don’t mock me!
てめえ ふざけた宣言してんじゃねえ！
ははは！ すまないねえ
でも恋人だからしょうがない！
Whoops, sorry,
but since I’m her boyfriend, I’ve no choice.
What’re you saying?!
うるせっ！ こ こ 恋人だからってな
何だよな
Just because you’re her boyfriend? As her friend, of course I’m–
友達だから当たり前…
うるさいぞ！
Shut up!
There are two extra cookies today.
今日は２個もクッキーが余るとはな
Chapter 21: "The Invitation"
That star-head…
あの星頭…
I’ll make you regret ever provoking me.
この俺を挑発したことを後悔させてやる
ふっ デートだと？
俺を誰だと思ってるんだ
A date, huh?
Who do you think I am?
Since you put it that way, I’ll show you…
そんなに言うなら見せてやる…
完璧なデートってやつをなあ
The perfect date!
However you look at it, I’m
なんせ俺は… パーフェクトだ！
perfect!
うっふふ さすが俺 何着ても似合うぜ
As I’d expect.
I look great no matter what I wear.
With this, if I invite Nino-san on a date…
これでニノさんをデートに誘えば…
A date, huh?
デートか… 生まれてから今まで
マンガのようにモテにモテた俺だが
Since I was born, I’ve been as popular as the guys in manga,
but I don’t have experience socializing with women.
女性との交際経験はない… からなあ
Could a relationship be “high risk, no return”?!
お付き合いだなんて
まさにハイリスク ノーリターン！
It’s a devil’s contract!
悪魔の契約だ！
It’s vexing, but I’ve never had a memorable Valentine’s Day.
毎年のバレンタインも
苦行としか言いようがなかった
And the 3,000 chocolates I receive…
３桁もの数のチョコレートを…
RETURN
This is Kou! All females in the school, please gather in the gym!
行です！ 全校女子！
体育館に集まって下さい！
RETURN
全て元の持ち主に返すのは
至難の業だったなあ…
Returning them all to the rightful owners was a nearly impossible task.
Recovery result: that chocolate has been returned to Ooba-san from Class 2.
It was her
just as I thought
鑑識の結果 このチョコレートは
２組の大場さんの物と一致しました！
Okay, that’s great! You get a raise!
よーし よくやった！ 昇給だあー！
What were those who didn’t leave their names with the chocolates trying to do?
名前書かない人とか
いったい何のつもりだろ…
ホワイトデーまでに３桁の女性に
借りを作りっぱなしでは
I could have unexpectedly died from an asthma attack by trying to return them all before White Day.
喘息の前に胃が消滅してしまうからな
That’s why I have no dating experience.
そんなわけでデートの経験はないが
I studied the materials all night.
Rose of Heracles
まあ 昨日一晩 資料に目を通したし
平気だろ
I should be fine.
Okay, off to the front line!
いざ 出陣！
Will it reach the sea?
あいつ海まで行けるかな
こんにちは ニノさん
Good afternoon, Nino-san.
The white rose that blooms in my heart
俺の心に咲く白いバラ
has come to steal your heart!
あなたのハートを
盗みに参上致しましたあっ！
Sorry
I’ll look forward to your next performance.
次回作に期待
うっく！ 一発芸じゃありませえーん！
It’s not a one-shot performance!
Chapter 22: "The Plan"
If it’s not a one-shot performance, what was it?
一発芸じゃないなら 何なんだ？
ふ ふふ… 見て分かりませんか？ニノさん
Can’t you tell, Nino-san?
These roses and name brand suit…
Everything is meant to attract you.
このバラもハイブランドのスーツも
全てあなたの気を引くための物
Yes. Today, I’ve come to invite you on a date.
そう 俺は今日
あなたをデートに誘いに来たのです！
What’s a date?
デートってなんだ？
くうっ… 何たる想定外
This is beyond my expectations.
Very impressive, Nino-san.
さすがだぜ ニノさん
How quickly you crashed my perfect plan.
早くもこの俺のパーフェクトプランに
亀裂を入れようとしてくるとはなあ
Date, right?
デート… か… 何だか禍々しい響きだな
Somehow, that sounds really ominous.
It’s not a plan that can be crushed with just this, though.
だが これしきのことで
潰されるプランではない！
So, what is it?
で 何なんだ？ 用がないなら
草舟制作に戻りたいんだが
If there’s nothing, I’d like to get back to making grass boats.
No, please wait.
いえ 待って下さい
Nino and me!
それは？
The pain from her spoiling my date plans still lingers,
デートプランを先にネタバレするのは痛いが
背に腹は代えられない
but nothing will change unless I rid her of her doubts.
When she hears this plan, I’m sure she’ll tell me she wants to go.
このプランを聞けば
きっと行きたいと言ってくれるはずだ
Please let me explain the date.
デートの説明をさせて頂きます！
First, we’ll go for a drive on Rainbow Bridge in this supercar.
まず２人でこのスーパーカーに乗り込み
レインボーブリッジでドライブ
OUR WORLD
Rainbow Bridge will be sectioned off just for our drive.
このドライブの間は２人のために
レインボーブリッジは封鎖
And from there, we’ll head to the best restaurant in Roppongi.
その足で六本木の
最高級レストランへと赴き…
I plan to entrust Japan to Ichinomiya-kun.
Lady
First
Prime Minister
市ノ宮君には この日本を
預けるつもりでいるんですよ 私は
Dinner in town with the Prime Minister.
首相を交えてのディナー
If Ichinomiya-kun hadn’t saved me from that situation back then…
あの時 市ノ宮君が
私を悪漢から救ってくれなかったら
Don’t mention it, Prime Minister. That’s in the past.
いいですよ首相 もうその話は
First
Lady
わたくし ちょっと歌いたくなっちゃった
I feel like singing.
ホーホケキョ
Sakura! Or isn’t it?
さーくーらーじゃないのおー
ニノちゃんも どうぞご一緒に
Nino-chan, come and join me.
There’ll be a first-rate orchestra,
超一流のオーケストラと
俺の美談などを肴に食事を楽しみ
Prime Minister
and we’ll have touching conversations about me to liven things up while we enjoy dinner.
After that,
そのあと… ヘリで東京湾上空まで飛び
we’ll fly in a helicopter all the way to Tokyo Bay.
This is a gift from me, to commemorate our first date.
初デートの記念に
僕からのプレゼントです
How lovely.
素敵…
とまあ… 以上が
デートというものになります
And well, that’s the end. That’s what a date is.
How’s that, Nino-san?
どうです？ ニノさん！
Great. It’s fun.
いい 楽しい
She accepted.
うけた！ 分かって頂けた！
She understood!
I find myself naturally talented at planning,
俺のプランニングの才能を思えば
当然のことだが
but I didn’t think she would be this pleased.
まさか こんなに喜んでくれるなんて…
Ah, they’re floating before my eyes!
はあ 目に浮かぶぜ… 星頭の悔しがる顔が
100パターンくらい まざまざと
A hundred different expressions of star-head’s frustrations.
Winning a bun-eating race with all my strength.
パン食い競争でも 全力で勝ち抜き
Placing first in a fiercely competitive entrance exam.
受験戦争に勝ち抜き
As I thought, even in the romance category, I’m an elite!
やはり 恋愛においても
俺はエリートだったのだ！
So, Recruit…
じゃあリクルート
Yeah! So, shall we get in the car–
ええ！ では早速車に がっ…
その紙芝居の続編 楽しみにしているな
I’ll look forward to the sequel of that picture story.
It’s not a picture story.
紙芝居じゃないし… つか…
Rather,
you’re actually going home after getting me this worked up?!
こんな浮かれトンチキになってる
人間を置いて よく帰れますねええー！
Chapter 23: "To the River Mouth"
カッコー カッコー
But besides that, your decision to go home was made too quickly!
それ以前に 帰る決断が早すぎますよ！
What, is this the sequel already?
何だ もう続編か？
No, it’s not.
違います！ デートっていうのは今の話を
俺とニノさんで実行することを言うんですよ
When it comes to a date, it includes both me and Nino-san.
Rec and me?
リクと私が？ 今のを？
Doing that thing earlier?
Yes, that’s right.
ええ そうです！ 聞いているだけで
夢のようだったでしょう？
Even the promo was like a dream, right?
However, I’ll change it all into a reality for you.
しかし！ 俺なら それを
実現させてあげられるんです！
一緒に行って下さいますよね？ニノさん
Won’t you come with me, Nino-san?
なぜ帰るんです？ 待って下さいよ！
Why are you going back?!
Please wait!
ああ まさか… お嫌なんですか？
Could it be… I chased you away?
Well, to do all that, we’d have to leave this river bed, wouldn’t we?
だって その話じゃ
この河川敷から出てるじゃないか
え… そりゃあ
お出かけするのがデートですし
Well, going out is part of a date.
I would really love to go,
行きたいのは やまやまだが
重力が… ほら
but the gravity is, well, you know…
重力？ 何です それ？
Gravity?
What’s that about?
考えてはみるが引力が
重力と見合ってごっちんこで
Now that I think of it, the magnetic gravitation corresponds with the gravity and integrates
強力なパワーで…
with the collaborated powers…
ええ？ 何です？ 要は何なんですか？
What’s that?
What is your concern?
Oh, and I’m a Venusian.
要は私は金星人だし…
が… 金星人トークきたあああー！
なぜ今？
She brought up being a Venusian!
Why now?
だ あ… 最近は何となく
話も噛み合うようになっていたのに
We’ve been able to converse with each other recently…
Hold it.
待てよ いつもニノさんが
金星の話を持ち出すのって…
When does Nino-san bring up the topic of Venus?
Oh, that’s the reason.
ああ だって そりゃあれだろう
お前は地球人だし 私は金星人だし
You’re an Earthling. I’m a Venusian.
As much as I am a Venusian, he is most definitely a kappa.
私が金星人なのと同じくらい
確実に村長は河童だ
Isn’t there a pattern in that ignorance?
なにかにノーを言う時なんじゃないのか？
That means Nino-san dislikes getting away from the riverbank
ということは… それほどニノさんにとって
この河川敷を出ることは嫌で
so badly that she doesn’t want to state the reason.
理由も言いたくないんだろうか…
はあ 分かりました
これは またの機会にしましょうか
I understand.
Shall we make it another time, then?
Are you sure?
いいのか？ お前その計画…
You planned all that.
It’s fine.
いいんです ニノさんに喜んで頂かなきゃ
パーフェクトとは言えませんから！
If Nino-san isn’t pleased with it, I can’t say it’s perfect.
In exchange,
その代わり… ニノさんの
行きたい所を教えてくれませんか？
will you tell me where you’d like to go, Nino-san?
Let’s go there!
そこへ行きましょう！
I’ll do my best to bring you anywhere.
俺が全力で
どこへだって連れていきますから！
Rec…
リク…
じゃあ 金星…
Then, Venus–
パス 大気圏内でお願いします！
Pass!
Please keep it within the atmosphere.
ぱふっ じゃあ… 河口
Then, the estuary.
Estuary?
河口？
I drifted some grass boats earlier.
さっき川に草舟を流していたんだ
Whether this river really connects to the sea,
この川は本当に海に繋がっていて
舟はちゃんと海に着いたんだろうか？
or if the boats reach the sea…
Would you go check that out with me?
一緒に見に行ってくれるか？
はい！ もちろんです ご一緒しますよ
Yes.
Of course.
I’ll accompany you.
Even though it is just the entrance to this river,
同じ河川敷内のお出かけでも
なにか一大決心をするかのように見えた
it seems this has taken a great deal of determination.
Oh yeah, Nino-san.
ああ そうだ ニノさん
Yeah?
その前に…
Before that…
これ 最初のプランの中で
Here.
It’s the dress for you that I included in my earlier plan.
ニノさんが着る予定だった
ドレスなんですけど
If you don’t mind, would you wear it?
よかったら着てみてくれませんか？
It’s been twenty minutes since then.
あれから20分…
こんなにかかるもんなのかあ？
Does it take that long?
Well, it has quite a complicated design.
まあ 結構複雑な作りだし
１人で着るのは大変だし…
It’d be difficult to put it on by herself.
あれ？ ていうか ニノさんが
１人で着れるわけなくないか？
Wait, can Nino even put it on by herself?
I’ve put it on.
着れた
大変だ…
This is bad.
Nino-san, maybe you should hold–
ニノさん！ やっぱりちょっと待っ…
What?
何だ？
う あ… あれ？
H-Huh?
That is already perfect.
それはもう完璧で
Has she ever worn clothes like this?
こういう服をよく着ることが
あったんだろうか？ とか
I just got a little curious about Nino-san’s past.
ニノさんの過去が少しだけ気になった
Chapter 24: "Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge"
I’m looking forward to this.
Everyone’s so eager, too.
It’s long-awaited, after all.
It sure is.
あの日夕暮れ
But the Village Chief is still the best.
I think so too.
You think so?
I was really surprised when I first saw it!
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
It certainly was surprising.
The Chief got into a cardboard box and closed it. Ten seconds later…
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
A young man in jeans popped out.
A great one-time illusion!
もう行かなくちゃ
I call it “Cardboard Transformation.”
この空泣き出す前に
I was really impressed.
I want to see that one-shot performance again!
I want to see it!
Nah, I can’t. That’s sacred to me.
サカサマになって
君の事探して
Oh, he’s here.
いつまでも僕らは
たどり着けないまま
I’ll do an impersonation.
Perry.
橋の下に立って
I can’t stand the smell of boats.
流れる渦に在って
Sorry
Creeper
If I return, seppuku is all that’s left for me.
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
An imitation.
Here I go!
A spike trap.
Sorry
Hideous
Has my star fallen to the ground?
I’ll go with a war joke.
Oh, why do provisioned meals taste so bad?
It’s so we’ll cooperate in hurrying to end the war so we can go home to our mothers’ home-made meals.
Oh, but compared with my mother’s home-cooked meals, the food here tastes better.
いやー 楽しみだなあ
みんな張り切ってましたからねえ
せっかくだもんな
せっかくですもんねえ
And the next day, that guy didn’t return from the front line.
でも やっぱり村長が頂点だよね！
僕もそう思う！
Sorry
Scum
えー そうかあ？
初めて見た時
すっごい びっくりしたもん！
確かに あれはねえ…
村長が段ボールの中に入って
ふたを閉めてから10秒後…
Hoshi will sing!
Next time: 4 Bridge.
You were under the bridge and decided what to have for lunch.
ふたをあけて出てくるのは ジーンズの似合う
好青年という大イリュージョン 一発芸！
If I don’t have you under my pillow, my days won’t be pleasant.
It’s always a happy day for me.
Love in the world!
And this is my golden world!
題して ザ 変身！ な
感動しましたよ
あの一発芸 またやって！
Illustration: Yuto
見たいよー
はは だめだめ あれは とっておきだから…
おっ 来たみたいだぞ
声真似 参るでござる ペリー
船ノニオイ 苦手デース
残された芸はもう切腹しか…
物真似！ 行くぜっ！
まきびし
夜空の星も地に落ちたか…
戦場ジョーク言います
はあ… どうしてこう
支給品の飯はまずいんだ
はっはっは
それはさっさと戦争を終わらせて
マムのうまい手料理を食えるように
俺達に努力させるためさ
おっと マムの手料理に比べたら
ここの飯のほうが うまいぜ
次の日 そいつは
前線から帰ってこなかった…
星 歌います！
次回 「４ BRIDGE」
朝起きたら きみがいて
ランチ食べたら きみがいて
枕の下にも きみがいる
そんな日々がラッキーデイ
俺にとっちゃハッピーデイ
言うなればエルドラド ぐわ はっ
俺だけのゴールデンワンレーン